Guide to the Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, DC records, 1980-2013 MS2230
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- 2015 donation materials, 1981-2013; MS2230 Series 7
  - Marketing, development, and production records, 1984-2004; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3
    - Advertisement and article clippings, 2010-2013; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Gay and Lesbian Chorus Publications, 2005, 2009; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Article clippings, 2009; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Metro Weekly Magazine, 2006, 2009, 2012; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - 1997 Season Brochure and Photographs, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Season Promotional Materials, 1994-2001, 2003-2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper clippings, 2006-2008, 2013; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - 2007 Production Materials, 2007, undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - 2007 Promotional and Production materials, 2007, undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - "American, the Fabulous!" Program, 2008 June; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Events Featuring GMCWDC, 2008-2009; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Newsletters [and other promotional materials], 2001, 2003, 2006-2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Spring Affairs, 2005, 2006, 2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - 2009 [2008-2009 Season Materials], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - 2008 [2008 Programs], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - 2007 [2007 Programs], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - 2006 [2006 Programs], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - 2005 [2005 Programs], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - 2004 [2004 Programs], 2004, undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - 2003 [2003 Programs], 2003, undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - 2002 [2002 Programs], 2002, undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - 2001 [2001 Programs], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - 2000 [2000 Programs], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - 2007-2008 and 2008-2009 Seasons, 2007-2009; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Production Book, Spring Concert 1992 [1/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Production Book, Spring Concert 1992 [2/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Production Book, Spring Concert 1999 ["Swellegant Elegance"] [1/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Production Book, Spring Concert 1999 ["Swellegant Elegance"] [2/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Production Book, May Concert 1992 [Tap Routines] [1/2], circa 1992-1993; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Production Book, May Concert 1992 [Tap Routines] [2/2], circa 1992-1993; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Production Book, April Concert 1994 [1/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Production Book, April Concert 1994 [2/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Production Book, Spring Concert 1996 [1/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Production Book, Spring Concert 1996 [2/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - "Hot Flashes" Newsletters, 1981-1983; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - "Hot Flashes" Newsletters [1/2], 1982-1985; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - "Hot Flashes" Newsletters [2/2], 1982-1985; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - "Hot Flashes" Newsletters, 1986-1991; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - FabYULEus! Programs and Inserts, 2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - 2008 [Programs & Show Materials from 2006], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - 2009 [Advertising Materials, Article Clippings, & Programs from 2005-2006] [1/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - 2009 [Advertising Materials, Article Clippings, & Programs from 2005-2006] [2/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - "Singing Free!"/Barbara Cook Concert and "Showboys!" Materials, 2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - "The Wizard of Oz" Programs and Audition Ads, 2006-2009; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - 2006-2007 Newsletter and Brochures, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - 2006-2007 Membership Brochure & 2008 Holiday Program, 2006-2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - "Mistletoe & Memories" Programs and Ads, 2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - "Showboys" Materials, 2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - "Spring Affair" Materials, 2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - 2007 Programs & Materials, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - 2007 Programs & Materials, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - 2007 Programs & Materials ["Songs of My Family"], Series 7 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - "Songs of My Family" materials, 2007; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - "Spring Affairs" Programs & "Singing Free" Newsletters, 2007; Series 7 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Programs - American Masterpieces [and "America, the Fabulous!" and "Great American Songbook"], 2007-2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Programs -That 80s Show, 2008; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - America, the Fabulous! program and Spring Affair ["Boots and Black Tie"], 2008; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Holiday 2008, Everything gAy to Z, 2008-2009, undated; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Programs/Publicity - 2008-2009 [Handouts, marketing materials, programs], Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Programs [and other marketing materials], 2009; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Grease Program, Love Concert [programs and marketing materials], 2009-2010; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Pink Nutcracker, Divas Programs, Spring Affair [other event and marketing materials], 2010; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - 2011-12 Programs ["The Kids are All Right," "Heart Throbs," "Red & Greene," Swing Affair], 2011-2012; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Press [Clippings, Promotional materials, "Hot Flashes" Newsletters, and Correspondence] [1/3], 2000-2001; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Press [Clippings, Promotional materials, "Hot Flashes" Newsletters, and Correspondence] [2/3], 2000-2001; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Press [Clippings, Promotional materials, "Hot Flashes" Newsletters, and Correspondence] [3/3], 2000-2001; MS2230 Serie 7 Subseries 3 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - 2001 Documents [Programs, Promotional materials, Capital Club Packet] [1/2], 2001-2002; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - 2001 Documents [Programs, Promotional materials, Capital Club Packet] [2/2], 2001-2002 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - 2002 programs, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - 2001-02 programs [including Rock Creek Singers and Potomac Fever], 2002, undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - 2002-03 programs [and Promotional materials], 2002-2003; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - 2002-03 membership directories, correspondence [Kennedy Center Honors, passing of Bob "Wanda Mae" Wonneberger] [1/2], 2002-2003; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - 2002-03 membership directories, correspondence [Kennedy Center Honors, passing of Bob "Wanda Mae" Wonneberger"] [2/2], 2002-2003; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - 2002-03 photos, press [Articles and clippings] [1/2], 2002-2003; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - 2002-03 photos, press [Articles and clippings] [2/2], 2002-2003; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - 2002-03 programs, publicity, 2002-2003; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - 2003-04 programs, publicity ["Wizard of Oz" and "Changing Hearts"], 2003-2004; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - 2003-04 programs, publicity ["Bye, Bye Birdie"], 2003-2004; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - 2003-04 programs, publicity, clippings ["Brassy Sassy Holiday," "Let Me Be the Music," and "You're a Good Man, Charlie Brown"], 2003-2004; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - 2003-04 clippings, correspondence, 2003-2004; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - 2004-05 season brochures, 2004-2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - 2004 clippings, publicity [GMCW Annual Cabaret], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - 2004 brochure, correspondence [Christmas cards & printing correspondence], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - 2004 programs, publicity ["Men in Tights"], 2004, undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - 2005 programs, newsletters, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - 2004-05 PF concert ["Let Us Entertain You" Potomac Fever and guests], 2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - 2004-05 Annual Report [and DC Pride Advertising], 2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - 2004-05 Newsletters, correspondence ["Naked Man" programs and promotional materials], 2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - 2004-05 Changing Hearts CD Package, 2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - 2005 Sweethearts of Cabaret [Programs & Printing Materials], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - 2005 Classical concert, press, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - 2005 Men, Men, Men programs, publicity [1/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - 2005 Men, Men, Men programs, publicity [2/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - 2005 Spring Affair [1/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - 2005 Spring Affair [2/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - 2005 Gala Chorus Concert Ad, FabYuleus! Publicity, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - 2004-05 Season Ads, 2004-2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - 2005 Fall Newsletter, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - 25th Anniversary materials [Logo designs and marketing materials], 2005; Series 7 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - 25th Anniversary t-shirt [Designs and correspondence], 2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Sondheim Cabaret [programs and marketing], 2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - FabYulous background materials ["FabYuleus!" marketing & press], 2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Press releases [1/2], 2005-2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Press releases [2/2], 2005-2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Advertising 2005-06 [1/2], 2005-2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Advertising 2005-06 [2/2], 2005-2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Spring Affair records [1/3], 2009-2010; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Spring Affair records [2/3], 2009-2010; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Spring Affair records [3/3], 2009-2010; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - 1998-99 Programs, clippings, and correspondence [1/4], 1998-1999; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - 1998-99 Programs, clippings, and correspondence [2/4], 1998-1999; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Archival Materials Used for 25th Anniversary History and DVD [1/5], 1981-2006; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Archival Materials Used for 25th Anniversary History and DVD [2/5], 1981-2006; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Archival Materials Used for 25th Anniversary History and DVD [3/5], 1981-2006; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Archival Materials Used for 25th Anniversary History and DVD [4/5], 1981-2006; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Archival Materials Used for 25th Anniversary History and DVD [5/5], 1981-2006; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - 1998-99 Programs, clippings, and correspondence [3/4], 1998-1999; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - 1998-99 Programs, clippings, and correspondence [4/4], 1998-1999; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - 1999-2000 Newsletters, Rosters, and Correspondence [1/3], 1990-2000; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - 1999-2000 Newsletters, Rosters, and Correspondence [2/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - 1999-2000 Newsletters, Rosters, and Correspondence [3/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - 1999-2000 programs [1/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - 1999-2000 programs [2/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - 1999-2000 programs [3/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - 2000-01 Rosters, Programs, and Press releases [1/3], 2000-2001; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - 2000-01 Rosters, Programs, and Press releases [2/3], 2000-2001; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - 2000-01 Rosters, Programs, and Press releases [3/3], 2000-2001; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - 2000-01 Press Releases, Programs, Newsletters [1/3], 2000-2001; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - 2000-01 Press Releases, Programs, Newsletters [2/3], 2000-2001; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - 2000-01 Press Releases, Programs, Newsletters [3/3], 2000-2001; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Programs from 1984, 1998, 1999, 2000 [1/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Programs from 1984, 1998, 1999, 2000 [2/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Programs from 1984, 1998, 1999, 2000 [3/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Programs from 1987, 1990, 1992, 1995 [1/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Programs from 1987, 1990, 1992, 1995 [2/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Programs from 1991, 1993, 1994, 1995, 1999 [1/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Programs from 1991, 1993, 1994, 1995, 1999 [2/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Programs from 1991, 1992, 1995, 1996 [1/3], 1989, 1991-1992, 1994-1998; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Programs from 1991, 1992, 1995, 1996 [2/3], 1989, 1991-1992, 1994-1998; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Programs from 1991, 1992, 1995, 1996 [3/3], 1989, 1991-1992, 1994-1998; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Programs from 1995, 1996, 1997, 1998 [1/2], 1995-1998, 2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Programs from 1995, 1996, 1997, 1998 [2/2], 1995-1998, 2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Programs from 1996, 1997, 2000 [1/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Programs from 1996, 1997, 2000 [2/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 1997-98 Miscellaneous correspondence, Board materials [and performance materials] [1/2], 1997-1998; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 1997-98 Miscellaneous correspondence, Board materials [and performance materials] [2/2], 1997-1998; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - 2003-2008 Misc. Spring Affair material, correspondence, contracts [and Board Materials] [1/3], 2004-2004, 2006-2009, 2013; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - 2003-2008 Misc. Spring Affair material, correspondence, contracts [and Board Materials] [2/3], 2004-2004, 2006-2009, 2013; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - 2003-2008 Misc. Spring Affair material, correspondence, contracts [and Board Materials] [3/3], 2004-2004, 2006-2009, 2013; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - 2005 Spring Affair [1/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - 2005 Spring Affair [2/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - 2007 Spring Affair, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Misc. documents: Arena Stage 2003; 20th Anniv. CD; Performance Agreements (samples) (1996); 2006-2007 Annual Report; FCPAA Reference Book 2008-2009; FY09 Lisner contracts; 2005 Insurance Policy [1/2], 1996, 2001-2005, 2007, 2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Misc. documents: Arena Stage 2003; 20th Anniv. CD; Performance Agreements (samples) (1996); 2006-2007 Annual Report; FCPAA Reference Book 2008-2009; FY09 Lisner contracts; 2005 Insurance Policy [2/2], 1996, 2001-2005, 2007, 2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - FY07 Spring Affair Notes, 2007; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Lisner Contracts, 2002-2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Montgomery College contract, 2004-2005, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Marvin Center Theatre, 2003, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Kennedy Center, 2002 [1/2], 2001-2003; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Kennedy Center, 2002 [2/2], 2001-2003; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Misc. documents: Kennedy Center 2006-2007; contracts 2005-2007 [1/4], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Misc. documents: Kennedy Center 2006-2007; contracts 2005-2007 [2/4], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Misc. documents: Kennedy Center 2006-2007; contracts 2005-2007 [3/4], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Misc. documents: Kennedy Center 2006-2007; contracts 2005-2007 [4/4], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - NYAPC Lease, 1992-1999 [New York Avenue Presbyterian Church], 1992, 1997-2000, 2002, 2004; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Sam Harris Mar 2005, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Performance venues brochures, 2003-2005, 2002-2004; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 1984-1985 programs, Potomac Fever, newsletters [1/3], 1984-1985, 2002; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 1984-1985 programs, Potomac Fever, newsletters [2/3], 1984-1985, 2002; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 1984-1985 programs, Potomac Fever, newsletters [3/3], 1984-1985, 2002; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 1985-1986 programs, newsletters, publicity [1/2], 1985-1986, undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 1985-1986 programs, newsletters, publicity [1/2], 1985-1986, undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 1986-1987 programs, newsletters, Capital Club [1/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - 1986-1987 programs, newsletters, Capital Club [2/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - 1987-1988 programs, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - 1988-1989 programs, newsletters [1/2], 1987-1989; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - 1988-1989 programs, newsletters [2/2], 1987-1989; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - 1989-1990 programs, newsletters, 1989-1991; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - 1990-1991 programs, newsletters [1/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - 1990-1991 programs, newsletters [2/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - 1991-1992 programs, newsletters, rosters, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - 1992-1993 programs, newsletters, news article, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - 1993-1994 newsletters, season brochure, program, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - 1994-1995 programs, newsletters [1/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - 1994-1995 programs, newsletters [2/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - 1995-1996 programs, newsletters, season brochure, chorus handbook [1/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - 1995-1996 programs, newsletters, season brochure, chorus handbook [2/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - 1995-1996 programs, newsletters, season brochure, chorus handbook [3/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - 1996-1997 programs, newsletters, season brochure, auction materials, roster [1/3], 1995-1997; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - 1996-1997 programs, newsletters, season brochure, auction materials, roster [2/3], 1995-1997; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - 1996-1997 programs, newsletters, season brochure, auction materials, roster [3/3], 1995-1997; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - 1996-1997 programs, newsletters, season brochure, gig sheets, news articles, rosters [1/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - 1996-1997 programs, newsletters, season brochure, gig sheets, news articles, rosters [2/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - 1996-1997 programs, newsletters, season brochure, gig sheets, news articles, rosters [3/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - 1997-1998 programs, newsletters, season brochure, cabaret, news articles, roster, camp materials, publicity materials [and Scandinavian tour] [1/4], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - 1997-1998 programs, newsletters, season brochure, cabaret, news articles, roster, camp materials, publicity materials [and Scandinavian tour] [2/4], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - 1997-1998 programs, newsletters, season brochure, cabaret, news articles, roster, camp materials, publicity materials [and Scandinavian tour] [3/4], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - 1997-1998 programs, newsletters, season brochure, cabaret, news articles, roster, camp materials, publicity materials [and Scandinavian tour] [4/4], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - 1997-1998 programs, newsletters, season brochure, 1995-1998; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - 1981-1982 SFGMC Ken Cen program, programs, press releases, news articles, correspondence, newsletters, gig sheets [1/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - 1981-1982 SFGMC Ken Cen program, programs, press releases, news articles, correspondence, newsletters, gig sheets [2/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - 1981-1982 SFGMC Ken Cen program, programs, press releases, news articles, correspondence, newsletters, gig sheets [3/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - 1982-1983 programs, minutes, newsletters, rosters, audition materials, financial statements [1/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - 1982-1983 programs, minutes, newsletters, rosters, audition materials, financial statements [2/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - 1982-1983 programs, minutes, newsletters, rosters, audition materials, financial statements [3/3], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - 1983-1984 programs, news articles, fan mail, seating charts, invoices, newsletters, financial statements, board applications, audition forms [1/4], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - 1983-1984 programs, news articles, fan mail, seating charts, invoices, newsletters, financial statements, board applications, audition forms [2/4], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 87, Folder 2)